{
    "subject": "resource/Pedder_Street",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:British_Hong_Kong",
    "human_readable": "Pedder Street is about British Hong Kong.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.926749587059021,
            "question": "What is the significance of Pedder Street in Hong Kong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6907667517662048,
            "question": "Is Pedder Street a famous street?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6740108728408813,
            "question": "What country is British Hong Kong associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6285414099693298,
            "question": "Where is Pedder Street located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6048917770385742,
            "question": "What type of place is Pedder Street?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5165659785270691,
            "question": "Is Pedder Street a popular tourist destination?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4752296209335327,
            "question": "Are there any notable buildings on Pedder Street?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4543161690235138,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the history of Pedder Street?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3076721429824829,
            "question": "What kind of businesses are typically found on Pedder Street?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30721160769462585,
            "question": "What is the atmosphere like on Pedder Street?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Pedder Street is about British Hong Kong.",
            "html": "dbpedia_855_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of businesses are typically found on Pedder Street?",
            "html": "dbpedia_855_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about the history of Pedder Street?",
            "html": "dbpedia_855_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any notable buildings on Pedder Street?",
            "html": "dbpedia_855_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_855_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_855_119.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_855_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_855_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_855_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_855_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_855_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_855_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_855_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_855_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThe documents clearly state that Pedder Street was established at the center of Hong Kong's commerce during the early colonial days and mentions Lieutenant William Pedder, Britain's first harbor master of Hong Kong.  Therefore, the statement \"Pedder Street is about British Hong Kong\" is supported by the provided information. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe documents mention Pedder Street as a major thoroughfare in the core of Hong Kong's Central District, and that it runs through areas with historical significance related to British colonial rule (e.g., the first harbour master of Hong Kong). There is no information to contradict this association."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Pedder Street is about British Hong Kong.\" The excerpts mention the street's historical context in the early colonial days, its connection to Britain (through Lieutenant William Pedder and the Nemesis), and its significance during the period of British control over Hong Kong."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}